

MUHAMMAD MEHBOOB FRONT-END DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

I have completed my graduation in BSSE in 2022. I am highly motivated to make my career in the software technology domain. My current focus is to have handson experience in web front-end development with React JS. Apart from front-end development, my plans are to learn the MERN stack to become a complete developer in web application development.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- JavaScript
- Responsive Web Design
- Front-end Skills: HTML5, CSS3
- Web Technologies: React Js
- Team Collaboration
- Redux
- CSS Framework: Material UI, Tailwind CSS, React-Bootstrap, Ant Design
- · Version Control System: Git, GitHub
- Axios
- Media Query
- React Routers
- Next JS

VITALS



+923042596211

☑ mehbooblilla007@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/muhammad-mehboob-9b20bb184

EXPERIENCE

INTERNATIONAL ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY, ISLAMABAD

IM-TOURIST PROJECT

09-2021 TO 08-2022

Develop a single web-based platform on which local or international travellers can approach several services and can get much information at a single point.

Features of Application,

- Have complete information.
- Have things to do at places.
- Have ratings and reviews.
- Provide reasonable prices.
- Trip guide.

TECHNOLOGIES: MERN STACK, ANT DESIGN, BOOTSTRAP, GITHUB, AXIOS,

IGNITE PAKISTAN

09-2022 TO PRESENT

Front end developer

Work in:

- Responsive Design
- Work with Rest API
- Team Collaboration
- Version control
- Tailwind CSS
- React JS
- Next JS

EDUCATION

BS Software Engineering

INTERNATIONAL ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY, ISLAMABAD

09-2018 TO 08-2022

Courses:

- Web Engineering Data Base
- Object Oriented
- Programming
- Data Structure & Analysis
- Mobile Application Developing

PERSONAL PROJECT

Personal Portfolio (08/2022)

Create a personal portfolio that describes personal details contact

MUHAMMAD MEHBOOB

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

information and project details.

Gym Management System (09/2021 - 01/2022)

This system helps the owner and Admin to maintain large data about users and their daily transactions in the gym. Also, suitable for users to automated attendance and online profile.

Basic Calculator (08/2021 - 08/2021)

Create a basic calculator app in react to take sum, divide, multiply, subtraction.

Food Menu (01/2022 - 02/2022)

Create a react template of a pizza shop to show pizza menu.

BMI Calculator (08/2022 - 08/2022)

CREATE A CALCULATOR TO FINE A BMI IN REACT JS.

CERTIFICATE

MERN-STACK ADVANCED

05-2022 TO 07-2022

Professional training in PSEB IT Industry Academia Program 2022 in MERN Stack

TECHNICAL DOMAIN

10-2021 TO 05-2022

Complete NFTP training in technical domain of HTMLCSS and JavaScript

LANGUAGES

- Urdu
- English
- Punjabi